{
    "id": "5d9386fdbfe74b1580092a3854a70d6c",
    "title": "Get And Go",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………… .. to work by car and Susie …………………… by train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go, go",
                "go, goes",
                "goes, goes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a2539d7a1f14081b6a99ebc5d412906"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s see who will ………………… there first?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6b2cda22b874fe2a900a5af076ad543"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… to see him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "got",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5c37bb10d254cc0bb9197f85524625b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although the train was late, I managed to …………………. to the meeting in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "77c5701edb474a92a3c203afddff348b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It wasn’t easy to ………………… through the crowd.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "got"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94ee62e1ac0c468788a73194313deeed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you tell me how to ……………………… to the post office?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65931587f2da4b7f8cde420b65990249"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had better ………………… going – it’s late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e094b4792b5e4f9e87a1f00ba7f68539"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………… late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "going",
                "getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aaf0f3b1ef9042218c3e3552592cec80"
        },
        {
            "question": "When do I ………………… to see your new baby?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc2047e301694b24b33fc0251d23a3de"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t ………………….. the car to start.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e211467606db4fda9f9e750d712c08bc"
        }
    ]
}